Strike Files of the U.S. Department of Justice, Pt. 1 on Microfilm 5897 mf
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Casefile 16-130. Continued (Reel 12)
  - Casefile 16-130. Subfile 57. Ohio (Southern District), 1919-1920; 13 (Reel 12)
    November 7, 1919-November, 19121. 132pp [frame 0492 repeated]. Subjects: Work stoppages; allegations of lawlessness and sabotage among immigrant coal miners; UMWA District 6 contrast negotiations with Eastern Ohio Operators Association; Joint Scale Committee of the Cantal Competitive Field; use of injunctions in labor disputes; regulation of coal prices; U.S. Railroad Administration; U.S Fuel Administration; Lever Act; U.S. Bituminous Coal Commission; refusal by coal operators to re-employ UMWA members; sympathy strike by international Brotherhood of Steam Shovel and Dredge Men. Begins at 0492.
  - Casefile 16-130. Subfile 58. Ohio (Northern District), 1920-1924; 14 (Reel 12)
    May 7, 1020-January 25, 1924. 264pp. [frame 0623 repeated] Subjects: Conspiracy indictment of offices of coal companies, operators associations, and UMWA; countersuit against Attorney General A. Mitchell Palmer, U.S. Attorney Frederick Van Nuys, and others; Sherman Act; Lever Act; U.S. Fuel Administration; mediation of labor disputes. Begins a 0623.
  - Casefile 16-130. Subfile 59. Oklahoma, 1919-1922; 15 (Reel 12)
    November 3, 1919-February 15. 1922. 33pp. [frame 0886 repeated] Subjects: Arbitration of labor disputes; Oklahoma Coal Operators Association; regulation of coal prices; UMWA District 21 contract negotiations; U.S. Fuel Administration; U.S. Railroad Administration. Begins at 0886.
- Casefile 16-130. Continued (Reel 13)
  - Casefile 16-130. Subfile 61. Oregon, 1919; 1 (Reel 13)
    November 15, 1919. 2pp. Subject: Regulation of coal prices. Begins at 0000.
  - Casefile 16-130. Subfile 62, Section 1. Pennsylvania, 1919-1920; 2 (Reel 13)
    November 1, 1919-January 14, 1920. 209pp. Subjects: U.S. Coal Commission; refusal by coal companies to re-employ UMWA members and abide by wage increases; Lever Act; UMWA Districts 2 and 5 contract negotiations; regulation of coal prices; U.S. Fuel Administration; National Retail Coal Merchants' Association; U.S. Railroad Administration; John Borphy, Phillip Murray, and Thomas Kennedy letters; Central Pennsylvania Coal Operates Association; use of injunctions in labor disputes; Pennsylvania State Federation of Labor. Begins 0002.
  - Casefile 16-130. Subfile 62, Section 2. Pennsylvania, 1920; 3 (Reel 13)
    January 14-September 1, 1920. 201pp. [frame 0211 repeated] Subjects: Mediation of labor disputes; Joint Scale Committee of the Central Competitive Field; Pittsburgh Coal Produces Association; U.S. Bituminous Coal Commission; U.S. Anthracite Coal Commission; UMWA factionalism and internal politics; proposed prosecution of Rinaldo Cappalino and other insurgent leaders of UMWA anthracite strike; regulation of coal prices; U.S. Fuel Administration; UMWA Districts 1 and 2 negotiations; John Brophy letters; U.S. Railroad Administration; Lever Act; shortage of railroad cars to service mines; refusal by coal companies to e-employ UMWA members. Begins at 0211
  - Casefile 16-130. Subfile 62, Section 3. Pennsylvania, 1920-1921; 4 (Reel 13)
    October 6, 1920-March 11, 1921. 11pp. [frame 0422 repeated] Subjects: U.S. Supreme Court decision overturning provisions of the Lever Act; U.S. Anthracite Coal Commission; complains regarding radicalism among UMWA members. Begins at 0411.
  - Casefile 16-130. Subfile 67. South Carolina, 1919-1920; 5 (Reel 13)
    November 2 1919-March 22-1920. 11pp. [frame 0422 repeated] Subjects: Regulation of coal prices; Lever Act; U.S. Fuel Administration. Begins at 0422.
  - Casefile 16-130. Subfile 69. South Dakota, 1919-1920; 6 (Reel 13)
    December 13, 1919-January 9, 1920. 7pp. [fames 0432 and 0473 repeated] Subjects: Regulation of coal prices; U.S. Fuel Administration; shortage of railroad cars for transporting coal from North Dakota; U.S. Railroad Administration. Begins at 0342.
  - Casefile 16-130. Subfile 70. Tennessee, 1919-1920; 7 (Reel 13)
    November 1, 1919-March 30, 1920. 186pp. Subjects: Regulation of coal prices; U.S. Fuel Administration; refusal by coal operators to abide by terms of strike settlement or re-employ UMWA members; Southern Appalachian Coal Operators Association; arbitration of labor disputes; UMWA District 19 contract negotiations; Tennessee Coal Operators Association; U.S. Bituminous Coal Commission; open shop versus closed shop issues; Lever Act; street car strike in Knoxville, Tennessee. Begins at 0437.
  - Casefile 16-130. Subfile 73. Texas, 1919-1920; 8 (Reel 13)
    November 1, 1919-Septembe 30, 1920. 38pp. [frame 0623 repeated] Subjects: Regulation of coal prices; U.S. Fuel Administration; U.S. Railroad Administration; Southwestern Regional Committee. Begins at 0623.
  - Casefile 16-130. Subfile 77. Utah, 1919; 9 (Reel 13)
    November 15-December 19, 1919. 20pp. [frame 0660 repeated] Subjects: Business support for DOJ policies regarding radicals; open shop versus closed shop issues; refusal by coal operators to re-employ striking UMWA members. Begins at 0660.
  - Casefile 16-130. Subfile 79. Virginia, 1919-1921; 10 (Reel 13)
    November 7, 1919-March 8, 1921. 7pp. [frame 0679 repeated] Subjects: American Farm Bureau Federation support for Sherman Act prosecution of coal operators for price-fixing; regulation of coal prices; U.S. Fuel Administration; U.S. Railroad Administration; U.S. Bituminous Coal Commission; diversion of coal cars on railroads as effect of strike. Begins at 0679.
  - Casefile 16-130. Subfile 81. Washington, 1919-1922; 11 (Reel 13)
    October 31, 1919-Januay 28, 1922. 123pp. [frame 0755 repeated] Subjects: Eviction of UMWA members from company houses; refusal by coal operators to abide by terms of strike settlement; UMWA District 10 contract negotiations; arbitration of labor disputes; U.S. Bituminous Coal Commission; Washington Coal Operators Association. Begins at 0755.
- Casefile 16-130. Continued (Reel 14)
  - Casefile 16-130. Subfile 81, Section 1. West Virginia, 1919; 1 (Reel 14)
    October 27-December 18, 1919. 317 pp. Subjects: refusal by coal operators to abide by terms of strike settlement UMWA Districts 17 and 29 contract negotiations; Kanawha Coal Operators Association; New River Coal Operators Association; grand jury investigators of Lever Act violations; use of injunctions in labor disputes; Northern West Virginia Coal Operators Association; U.S. Fuel Administration; U.S. Railroad Administration; Winding Golf Coal Operators Association; controversy over implementation of the check-off system; open shop versus closed shop issues; arrest and deportation proceedings against radical immigrant laborers; alleged IWW activities; UMWA strike benefits. Begins at 0000.
  - Casefile 16-130. Subfile 81. Section 2. West Virginia, 1919-1920; 2 (Reel 14)
    December 11, 1919-March 17, 1920. 262pp. Subjects: Regulation of coal prices; U.S. Fuel Administration; U.S. Railroad Administration; U.S. Bituminous Coal Commission; Lever Act; UMWA Districts 17 and 29 contract negotiations; New River Coal Operators Association; refusal by coal operators to abide by terms of strike settlement; controversy over implementation of the check- off system. Begins at 0317.
  - Casefile 16-130. Subfile 3. West Virginia, 1920-1921; 3 (Reel 14)
    March 22, 1920-October 24, 1921. 165pp. Subjects: Jailings of UMWA District 29 members in Logan, Mingo, and McDowell Counties, West Virginia; violence and intimidation declaration of martial law by U.S. President Warren G. Harding; Secretary of Commerce Herbert Hoover report on arbitration of labor disputes; open shop versus closed shop issues; Coal Operators Association of the Williamson Field; Logan County Coal Operators Association; reports on activities of Robert Minor by Francis Ralston Welsh; requests for use of federal troops; union requests for DOJ investigation of conditions; use of injunctions in labor disputes; U.S. Marshal deployment of special agents; refusal to re-employ and eviction of UMWA District 17 members from company houses in Kentucky and West Virginia; open shop versus closed shop issues; private detective agencies; U.S. Bituminous Coal Commission; Lever Act; regulation of coal prices. Begins at 0589.
  - Casefile 16-130. Subfile 83. Section 4. West Virginia, 1921-1924; 4 (Reel 14)
    October 22, 1921-December 5, 1924. 124pp. Subjects: Dismissal of charges against members of UMWA Districts 17 and 29 in Logan and Mingo Counties, West Virginia; U.S. Marshal deployment of special deputies and explanation of expenses; use of injunctions in labor disputes; corruption and fraudulent elections by sheriffs of Logan and Mingo Counties, West Virginia; civil law suits brought against UMWA District 17 by coal operators; open shop versus closed shop issues; prosecution of violators of martial law degree; War Department report on authority for use of federal troops; violence and intimidation; Logan County Coal Operators Association and Coal Operators Association of the Williamson Field refusal to recognize UMWA or abide by terms of strike settlement; union requests for DOJ investigation of conditions and dismissal of charges against UMWA members; America Civil Liberties Union interest in case. Begins at 0754.
  - Casefile 16-130. Subfile 85. Wisconsin, 1919-1920; 5 (Reel 14)
    December 2, 1919-March 26, 1920. 16pp. Subjects: Regulation of coal prices; U.S. Bituminous Coal Commission; U.S. Fuel Administration. Begins at 0878.
  - Casefile 16-130. Subfile 87. Wyoming, 1919-1920; 6 (Reel 14)
    November 8, 1919-January 6, 1920. 52pp. Subjects: Local union strikes; DOJ prosecution of radicals; regulation of coal prices; U.S. Marshal deployment of special deputies; U.S. Railroad Administration; Central Western Regional Coal Committee; use of injunctions in labor disputes; deportation of radical immigrant laborers; U.S. Fuel Administration. Begins at 0894.
- Casefile 16-135 through 16-143 (Reel 15)
  - [New York City Harbor Strike] Casefile 16-135, 1919-1921; 1 (Reel 15)
    Subfile 1. October 13, 1919-May 13, 1921. 204pp. Subjects: U.S. Shipping Board; alleged radical activities; general strikes; strikebreakers; arbitration of labor disputes; minutes of conference of A. Mitchell Palmer concerning Railroad and New York Harbor Strike; International Longshoremen's Association in New York; U.S. Railroad Administration; strike of seamen in Galveston, Texas; U.S. Department of Labor statistics concerning strikes; DOJ refusal to intervene for protection of interstate committee. Begins at 0000.
  - [Puerto Rico Longshoremen's Strike] Casefile 16-135-65, 1920; 2 (Reel 15)
    June 9-August 1920. 43pp. Subjects: Lever Act; prosecution of longshoremen in Puerto Rico; violence and intimidation. Begins at 0204.
  - [Galveston, Texas, Longshoremen's Strike] Casefile 16-135-75, 1920; 3 (Reel 15)
    May 24-July 6, 1920. 22pp. Subjects: Declaration of martial law; mass meetings; strikebreakers; Texas Chamber of Commerce; International Longshoremen's Association; refusal by ship owners to arbitrate dispute. Begins at 0247.
  - [Utica, New York, Textile Workers Strike] Casefile 16-137, 1919; 4 (Reel 15)
    November 6-10, 1919. 5pp. Subjects: DOJ investigation of organizers of the Amalgamated Association of Textile Workers; Espionage Act; immigrant labor. Begins at 0269.
  - [Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America Strike] Casefile 16-138, 1919-1920; 5 (Reel 15)
    November 7,1919-December 15, 1920. 8pp. Subjects: Organization activities in Illinois, Massachusetts, New Jersey, and New York; activities of Sidney Hillman and A.J. Muste; Amalgamated Textile Workers of America; Bureau of Investigation letter of J. Edgar Hoover; mill owners' requests for DOJ support; private detective agencies; radical activities; National Association of Wool Manufacturers; arbitration of labor disputes; contract negotiations; National Association of Retail Clothiers; International Ladies Garment Workers Union contract negotiations in Toledo, Ohio; radical activities of the Cloak Maker's Union. Begins at 0274.
  - [Marine Workers Strike] Casefile 18-140, 1920-1921; 6 (Reel 15)
    [Subfile 0.] March 18, 1920-September 12, 1921. 78pp. Subjects: Use of injunctions in labor disputes; U.S Shipping Board; organizational activities in California, Florida, Maryland, New York, and South Carolina; immigrant labor; arbitration of labor disputes; contract negotiations; violence and intimidation; National marine Engineers' Protective Association; Masters, Mates, and Pilots Union of the Pacific. Begins at 0322.
  - Casefile 16-140. Subfile 22. California, 1921-1922; 7 (Reel 15)
    May 19, 1921-June 2,1922. 15pp. Subjects: Use of injunctions in labor disputes; organization activities in California; U.S. Shipping Board; general strike in San Francisco Harbor. Begins at 0400.
  - Casefile 16-140. Subfile 32. Louisiana, 1922; 8 (Reel 15)
    May 10, 1921-February 14, 1922. 38pp. Subjects: Use of injunctions in labor disputes; organized activities in Louisiana; U.S. Shipping Board; violence and intimidation. Begins at 0415.
  - Casefile 16-140. Subfile 51. New York, 1921; 9 (Reel 15)
    May 14-20, 1921. 21pp. Subjects: Use of injunctions in labor disputes; U.S. Shipping Board; DOJ cooperation with ship owners. Begins at 0453.
  - Casefile 16-140. Subfile 61. Oregon, 1921; 10 (Reel 15)
    May 18-August 12, 1921. 21pp. Subjects: Use of injunctions in labor disputes; U.S. Shipping Board. Begins at 0460.
  - Casefile 16-140. Subfile 67. Southern Carolina, 1921; 11 (Reel 15)
    May 5-October 10, 1921. 12pp. Subjects: U.S. Shipping Board; use of injunctions in labor disputes; violence and intimidation. Begins at 0481.
  - Casefile 16-140. Subfile 79. Virginia, 1921; 12 (Reel 15)
    May 7-June 10, 1921. 39pp. Subjects: Use of injunctions in labor disputes; U.S. Shipping Board; violence and intimidation. Begins at 0493.
  - Casefile 16-130. Subfile 82A. Washington, 1921; 13 (Reel 15)
    May 5-June 29, 1921. 53pp. Subjects: Use of injunctions in labor disputes; U.S. Shipping Board; violence and intimidation. Begins at 0532.
  - Casefile 16-140. Subfile 82B. Washington, 1921; 14 (Reel 15)
    May 7-August 6, 1921. 36pp. Subjects: Use of injunctions in labor disputes; U.S. Shipping Board; violence and intimidation. Begins at 0585.
  - [National Railroad Strike] Casefile 16-142, 1920; 15 (Reel 15)
    February 10-March 29, 1920. 70pp. Subjects: U.S. Railroad Administration use of injunctions in labor disputes. Begins at 0621.
  - [New York Harbor Workers Strike] Casefile 16-143, 1920-1922; 16 (Reel 15)
    April 8, 1920-May 8, 1922. 230pp. Subjects: DOJ policy regarding application of the Adamson eight-hour law to harbor workers in New York; U.S. Railroad Labor Board; Erie Railroad Company subvention of the Phoenix Transfer Company to escape provisions of the eight-hour-law
- Casefile 16-145 (Reel 16)
  - [National Railroad Yardmen's Strike] Casefile 16-145, Section 1, 1920; 1 (Reel 16)
    April 8-23, 1920. 284pp. Subjects: U.S. Railroad Labor Board; citizen complaints concerning shutdown of transportation system; Lever Act prosecutions; allegations of IWW involvement; private detective agencies; Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen; obstruction of U.S. mail and interference with interstate commerce, anti-labor legislation in U.S. Congress. Begins at 0000.
  - Casefile 16-145. Section 1, Previously Restricted Materials, 1920; 2 (Reel 16)
    April 7, 1920. 4pp. Subject: Report on situation in Springfield, Illinois railroad yards. Begins at 0284.
  - Casefile 16-145. Special Enclosures, 1920-1921; 3 (Reel 16)
    April 13, 1920-March 2, 1921. 24pp. Subjects: Partial list of striking railroad employees in Pennsylvania; U.S. Railroad Labor Board. Begins at 0288.
  - Casefile 16-145. Special Section, 1920; 4 (Reel 16)
    April 10-28, 1920. 568pp. Subjects: Lists of names and addresses of all striking employees of railroads in Delaware, Illinois, Indiana, Kentucky, Maryland, Michigan, New Jersey, New York, Pennsylvania, and Ohio; U.S. Railroad Administration; union organization. Begins at 0312.
- Casefile 16-145. Continued (Reel 17)
  - Casefile 16-145. Special Section cont, 1920; 1 (Reel 17)
    April 13-23, 1920. 391pp. Subjects: Lists of names and addresses of all striking employees of railroads in Delaware, New Jersey, New York, Pennsylvania, and Ohio; U.S. Railroad Administration; union organization. Begins at 0000.
  - Casefile 16-145. Section 2, 1920; 2 (Reel 17)
    April 14-August 2, 1920. 408pp. Subjects: Jurisdictional dispute between Yardmen's Association and Railroad Brotherhoods; Democratic National Convention; alleged IWW involvement; petitions for federal mediation of strike; AFL Railway Employees' Department; union organization; violence and intimidation; citizens complaints concerning shutdown of transportation system; lists of striking railroad employees in Indiana, Illinois, New Jersey, New York, Ohio, and Pennsylvania; American Civil Liberties Union interest in strike; Lever Act prosecutions; obstruction of U.S. mail and interference with interstate commerce. Begins at 0391.
  - Casefile 16-145. Section 2, Previously Restricted Materials, 1920; 3 (Reel 17)
    April 24-June 29, 1920. 6pp. Subjects: AFL Railway Employees' Department; mediation of labor disputes; Lever Act prosecutions. Begins at 0799.
  - Casefile 16-145. General, Special Correspondence, 1920; 4 (Reel 17)
    April 3-23, 1920. 31pp. Subjects: U.S. Railroad Labor Board; reports from railroad companies on labor problems and inception of strike. Begins at 0805.
- Casefile 16-145 End through 16-148 (Reel 18)
  - Casefile 16-145. Special Encounters, 1920; 1 (Reel 18)
    February 12-August 7, 1920. 250pp. Subjects: U.S. Railroad Labor Board; mediation of labor disputes; lists of crew shifts and percent of employees at work on the Baltimore and Ohio Railroad; Bureau of Investigation reports on national railroad strike; U.S. Railroad Administration; United Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Employees and Railway Shop Laborers; U.S. Railroad Labor Board; use of injunctions in labor disputes; alleged IWW influence in strike; Lever Act prosecutions; Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen; Communist Party of America; Communist Labor Party of America; Comintern. Begins at 0000.
  - Casefile 16-145. Section 3, 1920-1925; 2 (Reel 18)
    June 24, 1920-August 2, 1925. 146pp. Subjects: Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen; U.S. Railroad Administration; U.S. Railroad Labor Board; mediation of labor disputes; ALF Railway Employes' Department; Interstate Commerce Commission; U.S. Chamber of Commerce; American Train Dispatchers Association; reports from confidential informants on union organization and radical activities; strikebreakers; violence and intimidation; Brotherhood Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen; private detectives. Begins at 0250.
  - Casefile 16-145. Section 3. Previously Restricted Materials, 1920; 3 (Reel 18)
    June 22-August 15, 1920. 31pp. Subjects: Reports from confidential informants on union organization and radical activities; private detectives; strikebreakers; violence and intimidation; Pennsylvania Labor Party; Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen. Begins at 0396.
  - [Exportation of Coal] Casefile 181092. Subfile 231, 1920-1923; 4 (Reel 18)
    June 14, 1920-August 23, 1923. 160pp. Subjects: Regulation of coal prices; Federal Fuel Distributor; Lever Act Prosecutions; Interstate Commerce Commission; alleged profiteering in sales of coal; Federal Trade Commission; National Coal Association; alleged shortage of railroad coal cars. Begins at 0437.
  - [National Railroad Yardmen's Strike] Casefile 16-145 cont. Subfile 1. Alabama, 1922; 5 (Reel 18)
    February 13, 1922. 14pp. Subjects: Report of the Director Federal of Railroads to the president of the United States covering the period of dates from the relinquishment of federal operations; U.S. Railroad Administration; financial mattes. Begins at 0587.
  - Casefile 16-145. Subfile 10. Arkansas, 1921-1923; 6 (Reel 18)
    February 21, 1921-January 26, 1923. 45pp. Subjects: Mob violence and intimidation against strikers; Citizens' Committee seizure of union records, investigation of arson against railroad property; and lynching of striker; U.S. Railroad Labor Boars; mediation of labor disputes; contract negotiations. Begins at 0601.
  - Casefile 16-145. Subfile 11. California (Northern District), 1921; 7 (Reel 18)
    March 21-26, 1921. 6pp. Subjects: Lever Act prosecutions; legal defense efforts. Begins at 0646.
  - Casefile 16-145. Subfile 12. California (Southern District), 1920-1924; 8 (Reel 18)
    April 26, 1920-Marcch 4, 1924. 64pp. Subjects: Leve Act prosecutions; constitutional law. Begins at 0652.
  - Casefile 16-145. Subfile 19. Georgia, 1921-1922; 9 (Reel 18)
    March 6, 1921-July 15, 1922. 163pp. Subjects: Bureau of Investigation reports; violence and intimidation; union boycott of businesses using railroad in dispute; strikebreakers; DOJ employment of former corporate counsel as special assistant for Sherman Act and arson prosecutions of union members; U.S. Railroad Labor Board; Interstate Commerce Commission; use of receivership as shield from labor expenses; DOJ subpoena of union records for use in prosecution; American Train Dispatchers Association; contract negotiations; mediation of labor disputes; constitutional law; Newlands Act; U.S. Post Office Department. Begins at 0716.
  - Casefile 16-15. Subfile 23. Illinois, 1920-1923; 10 (Reel 18)
    July 17, 1920-January 2, 1923. 149pp. Subjects: Lever Act prosecutions; Chicago Yardmen's Association; violence and intimidation; Association of Railway Executives; United Association of Railway Employees of North America; AFL Railway Employees' Department; Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen; DOJ efforts to break "outlaw" railroad strike; Bureau of Investigation reports on surveillance of union meetings and nationwide strike activities; strikebreakers. Begins at 0879.
  - Casefile 16-145. Subfile 23, Enclosure Section. Illinois, 1920; 11 (Reel 18)
    April 1-27, 1920. 59pp. Subjects: Draft temporary restraining order and bill of complaint against officers and members of the Chicago Yardmen's Association and the United Enginemen's Association; strike for increase in wages and eight hour day; union organization; mass meetings; reports on activities of union leaders; private detectives; contract negotiations; list of crews working on various railroads; strikebreakers. Begins at 1028.
  - Casefile 16-145. Subfile 29. Kansas, 1921; 12 (Reel 18)
    March 14-15, 1921. 3pp. Subjects: U.S. Railroad Administration. Begins at 1087.
  - Casefile 16-145. Subfile 35 Maryland, 1920; 13 (Reel 18)
    June 16-22, 1920. 4pp. Subjects: U.S. Railroad Administration; union organization. Begins at 1090.
  - Casefile 16-145. Subfile 37. Enclosure Section. Michigan, 1920; 14 (Reel 18)
    February 10-12, 1920. 40pp. Subjects: Draft preliminary injunction of bill of complaint against officers and members of the United Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Employees and Railway Shop Laborers; reports on activities of union leaders; U.S. Railroad Administration; mediation of labor disputes. Begins at 1094.
  - Casefile 16-145. Subfile 42. Missouri, 1920; 15 (Reel 18)
    August 11-25, 1920. 5pp. Subjects: Lever Act prosecutions; violence and intimidation. Begins at 1134.
  - Casefile 16-145. Subfile 48. New Jersey, 1920-1922; 16 (Reel 18)
    May 20, 1920-June 22, 1922. 5pp. Subjects: Lever Act prosecutions; violence and intimidation. Begins at 1139.
  - Casefile 16-145. Subfile 51. New York, 1920; 17 (Reel 18)
    April 19-May 11, 1920. 24pp. Subjects: Obstruction of U.S. mails; U.S. Post Office Department. Begins at 1144.
  - Casefile 16-154. Subjects 54. North Carolina, 1920; 18 (Reel 18)